Moises Miguel

Cell: (952)-220-9630

Email:

moisesmigueledu@gmail.com

PROJECTS

GarageShare — Full Stack Web App

GarageShare is a Mean Stack web App that helps people rent equipment from local people. Users can register and post equipment. Users have the option to set a price range for a day, week or month. Users can also search for equipment based on their desired mile radius. Once an equipment has been chosen, the user is able to send a quick message to the owner via email and SMS.

GetUp StandUp — Full Stack Web App

GetUp standup is a non-profit organization that helps match up recently injured individuals from spine related injuries to those who have had a similar experience in the twin cities. They used to match people by using google docs and reading through every single application. It was very time consuming for Robert Wudlick (Founder of organization). We created a signup web application that uses the user's data to determine who is the best match according to their needs and similarities. I have found this to be a very rewarding project because I was able to use my passion for technology to help those in need.

EXPERIENCE

IHOP, Apple Valley — Server

2015 - 2017

I started working at IHOP as a cook. With in 2 months my manager gave me the opportunity to serve.I greeted customers and assisted them with their drinks and food, as well as making sure everything was stocked. I also cleaned and labeled everything to make sure we were serving the customer the freshest food.

Express Temp Agency, Lakeville — Warehouse Staff

2015 - 2017

As a temporary worker I was placed at multiple locations in the twin cities working in warehouses with multiple duties. Duties included: Loading

Technical Skills

MEAN STACK

Mongo

Express

Angular

Node.js

JavaScript es6

jQuery

GIT

HTML5/CSS3

Bootstrap

API

Socket.io

SQL

Twilio

NodeMailer

LANGUAGES

Native Spanish - English

trucks, Keeping track of inventory, importing and exporting goods.

Pearson Construction, Twin Cities —Assistant

2015 - 2015

I was the assistant to the owner of Pearson Construction. I was in charge of helping in the construction and renovation of homes. My duties included demolition, cleaning up, measurements, gathering materials and assisting Pearson.

EDUCATION

Prime Digital Academy, Minneapolis — FullStack Software Development

Normandale Community College, Bloomington — *Computer Science*

Lakeville South High School, Lakeville — *Diploma*